Okay, let's move on to strategy. Our online promotion
좋아, 전략으로 넘어가자. 우리의 온라인 프로모션
Mobile social media from usage survey
사용 설문 조사에서 얻은 모바일 소셜 미디어
People aged 20 to 30 years old
20~30세의 사람
Instagram is social media. most used by people
인스타그램은 소셜미디어이다. 사람들이 가장 많이 사용하는
Among people in their 30s and 40s, the most popular platform is Cocoa Story.
30~40대에게 가장 인기 있는 플랫폼은 코코아스토리다.
Followed by B Band and U Community.
B밴드, U커뮤니티가 뒤를 이었다.
Instagram users are mostly male
인스타그램 사용자는 대부분 남성이다
As for age
나이에 관해서는
Most users are teenagers.
대부분의 사용자는 청소년입니다.
"PR Joea"
"홍보조아"
Are you tired after waiting for so long?
너무 오래 기다리다 지치셨나요?
What about your president?
대통령은 어떻습니까?
Coming soon.
곧 출시됩니다.
They were the last to fight him.
그들은 그와 마지막으로 싸웠습니다.
You're used to this kind of thing.
당신은 이런 일에 익숙합니다.
Who puts on an honest face to encourage me
솔직한 표정으로 나를 격려해주는 사람
Right here, my president.
바로 여기요, 대통령님.
Yuncheng
윈청
I don't need such encouragement.
그런 격려는 필요 없어요.
- Yun Qiao, are you ready? - Yes.
- 윤교야, 준비됐어? - 예.
OK, let's go.
확인 가자.
The last speaker is PR Joa.
마지막 연사는 PR Joa입니다.
"Marketing Team Leader Gao Dongjun"
"마케팅팀장 가오동준"
a while.
잠시.
Who will introduce it?
누가 소개해줄까요?
Shouldn't the president be the one in attendance?
대통령이 참석해야 하는 것 아닌가요?
Yes, it’s not me, it’s Manager Park Yoon-joo...
네, 제가 아니고 박윤주 매니저님이십니다...
Yes, the chairman is the host.
네, 의장이 호스트입니다.
CEOs of other companies do the same.
다른 회사 CEO들도 마찬가지다.
Manager Park was the one who came up with this plan. So she will present it herself.
이 계획을 세운 사람은 박 감독이다. 그래서 그녀는 그것을 직접 발표할 것입니다.
The president himself said it.
대통령이 직접 말했다.
Everyone lets everyone else come up with plans.
모두가 다른 사람이 계획을 세우도록 허용합니다.
Is it that difficult to understand?
이해하기가 그렇게 어렵나요?
Or are you not ready to present yet?
아니면 아직 발표할 준비가 안 되셨나요?
Boss Song called Senior Jin?
송사장님이 진선배한테 전화하셨어요?
To attack her?
그녀를 공격하려고?
So she's really here?
그럼 그 사람이 정말 여기 온 걸까요?
Well, life is hard like that.
뭐, 인생은 그만큼 힘든 것 같아요.
Yes, then I will introduce it myself.
네, 그럼 제가 직접 소개하겠습니다.
《Seyuu》
《세용》
Not prepared. Also, there is a lack of sincerity.
준비되지 않았습니다. 또한 성실성이 부족합니다.
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
sorry.
죄송합니다.
I didn't mean to hear it.
나는 그것을 듣고 싶지 않았습니다.
yes...
예...
If you choose not to wear makeup, I understand.
화장을 안 하기로 결정했다면 이해해요.
in daily life
일상 생활에서
But this is just cosmetic work.
그러나 이것은 단지 미용 작업일 뿐입니다.
This is a press conference. new cosmetics
기자회견입니다. 새로운 화장품
You are the president of the company that has come to bid.
당신은 입찰하러 온 회사의 사장입니다.
But still...
하지만 아직...
That is...
그건...
So, have you tried our products?
그럼 저희 제품을 사용해 보셨나요?
In this way, I will trust you. How can you do this job?
이로써 나는 당신을 믿을 것입니다. 이 일을 어떻게 할 수 있나요?
Sorry, I have sensitive skin.
죄송합니다. 저는 피부가 민감합니다.
I hope you can understand.
나는 당신이 이해할 수 있기를 바랍니다.
Haven't used it yet.
아직 사용하지 않았습니다.
But this is really your problem.
그러나 이것은 정말로 당신의 문제입니다.
Damn it
젠장
Am I asking for too much?
내가 너무 많은 것을 요구하고 있는 걸까?
I think the expectation is to be professional. There's nothing wrong with acting professional.
나는 전문가가 될 것으로 기대한다고 생각합니다. 전문적으로 행동하는 데에는 아무런 문제가 없습니다.
It's so uncomfortable.
너무 불편해요.
Mr. Song, what's going on? You act like a brat.
송 씨, 무슨 일이에요? 당신은 말괄량이처럼 행동합니다.
This is a hot topic. Just got my Ph.D.
이것은 뜨거운 주제입니다. 방금 박사 학위를 받았습니다.
Captain Song Sun Tae
송선태 대위
I am Park Yoon Jo from PR Jo Ah.
PR 조아 박윤조 입니다.
What I asked is outdated. is there anything you can do?
내가 요청한 내용은 오래되었습니다. 당신이 할 수 있는 일이 있나요?
Other company presidents: Do you also wear makeup?
다른 회사 사장들: 화장도 하시나요?
They're all men, right?
다들 남자죠?
Oh, or because he's a man. So I don’t have to dress up.
아, 아니면 남자라서요. 그래서 옷을 입을 필요가 없어요.
If you are a true professional
당신이 진정한 전문가라면
You should wear makeup. Let's introduce cosmetic work.
화장을 해야 합니다. 화장품 작품을 소개하겠습니다.
Is this true regardless of whether you wear clothes or not ?
옷을 입든 안 입든 상관없이 이것이 사실인가요 ?
May I have your name?
제가 이름을 물어봐도 될까요?
Park Yoon Joo
박윤주
Let’s take a closer look.
좀 더 자세히 살펴보겠습니다.
Yes, then let's get started.
네, 그럼 시작해 보겠습니다.
"Happy dance"
"행복한 춤"
“Shochu”
“소주”
By the way, does the President have sensitive skin?
그런데 대통령님 피부가 예민하신가요?
nothing.
아무것도 아님.
I have had great skin since birth.
나는 태어날 때부터 피부가 좋았습니다.
Compared to the body, it's just healthy skin.
몸에 비하면 그저 건강한 피부일 뿐입니다.
"I wanted to ask something old-fashioned. Is there anything you can do?"
"옛날식으로 물어보고 싶었는데 혹시 할 수 있는 일이 있나요?"
Yunjo is braver than I thought.
윤조는 생각보다 용감해요.
It's not easy to do that under those circumstances .
그런 상황에서는 그렇게 하기가 쉽지 않습니다 .
I can not do anything.
나는 아무것도 할 수 없습니다.
This has nothing to do with courage.
이것은 용기와는 아무런 관련이 없습니다.
I feel so bad.
기분이 너무 안 좋아요.
At least she should give a speech. Gather experience
적어도 그녀는 연설을 해야 한다. 경험을 쌓다
He said that the president of another company showed me this work in person.
다른 회사의 사장이 직접 이 작품을 보여줬다고 하더군요.
The president did the right thing.
대통령은 옳은 일을 했습니다.
In addition, I also practice regularly myself.
게다가 나 역시 정기적으로 연습을 하고 있다.
It was a good experience.
좋은 경험이었습니다.
Their attitude is very bad.
그들의 태도는 매우 나쁩니다.
How many more decades have passed? Power-mad attitudes may never change.
몇십년이 더 지났나요? 권력에 미친 태도는 결코 변하지 않을 수 있습니다.
Because we are just supporting actors.
우리는 조연배우일 뿐이니까.
In fact we know and know
사실 우리는 알고 또 알고
But you still have to do your best. In case they don't like us...
하지만 여전히 최선을 다해야 합니다. 만약 그 사람들이 우리를 좋아하지 않는다면...
Makes me sad.
나를 슬프게 만들어.
Oh my Yunqiao
아, 윤차오
Sorry, I'm late.
미안 늦었 어.
Mr. Earth Communications...
미스터 어스 커뮤니케이션즈...
Can I sit with you?
같이 앉아도 될까요?
Yes
예
I haven't seen my senior for a long time.
나는 오랫동안 선배를 보지 못했다.
I said I had to come over for a drink.
술 한잔하러 오라고 했어요.
- Yeah- So I asked if I could be in the band too.
- 네- 그래서 나도 밴드에 들어갈 수 있냐고 물었어요.
Oh, yes, um...
아, 응, 음...
Come sit here.
여기로 와서 앉으세요.
Ah right?
아 그렇죠?
Did you have dinner with your employees?
직원들과 저녁식사하셨나요?
Yes, I've eaten it.
네, 먹어봤습니다.
It's like they want to go drinking together.
같이 술 마시러 가고 싶은 모양이다.
Oh, no wonder you call me when you have time.
아, 시간이 나면 나한테 전화하는 게 당연하지 .
Not because we miss each other.
우리가 서로 그리워서가 아닙니다.
Come on, I'm thinking about it.
자, 생각 중이에요.
I would like to take care of you myself.
개인적으로 당신을 돌보고 싶습니다.
I should make up for my mistakes.
나는 내 실수를 만회해야 한다.
That's not to say. You should bring your corporate card to use.
그런 말은 아닙니다. 법인카드를 지참하셔야 이용이 가능합니다.
Using your own card is another story.
자신의 카드를 사용하는 것은 또 다른 이야기입니다.
I can assure you, this is my card.
장담할 수 있습니다. 이것은 내 카드입니다.
But wait.
하지만 기다려.
Why did you come to feed me? Pay for my shirt.
왜 나한테 밥 주러 왔어? 내 셔츠 값을 지불하세요.
You should give me money.
나에게 돈을 주어야합니다.
What? What's going on with you two?
무엇? 너희 둘에게 무슨 일이 있는 거야?
What shirt?
무슨 셔츠?
I had a chocolate latte disaster this morning.
오늘 아침에 초콜렛 라떼 재난을 겪었습니다.
Oh, that's where you buy new shirts?
아, 거기서 새 셔츠를 사나요?
You bought it with my credit card.
내 신용카드로 샀잖아.
This is our company's business card.
이것은 우리 회사의 명함입니다.
Then pay for the food.
그런 다음 음식 비용을 지불하십시오.
Let's drink.
마시자.
"'Celtics' Evaluation Form, Promotional Auction Presentation."
"'셀틱스' 평가서, 프로모션 경매 프레젠테이션."
"Celtics Online and Offline Campaign Plan PR Joa"
"셀틱스 온라인 및 오프라인 캠페인 기획 PR 조아"
You're used to this kind of thing.
당신은 이런 일에 익숙합니다.
Put on an honest face and give me encouragement.
솔직한 표정으로 격려해 주세요.
I do not need...
난 필요 없어...
Such encouragement
이런 격려
"Call Yun Qiao."
"윤교에게 전화해."
Unable to contact destination number.
대상 번호에 연결할 수 없습니다.
Please leave a message after the beep...
삐 소리 후에 메시지를 남겨주세요...
Oh, you haven't come back yet?
아, 아직 안 돌아오셨나요?
I thought we all went back.
나는 우리 모두가 돌아갔다고 생각했다.
Don't be too happy yet. I'm not going to have a drink.
아직은 너무 기뻐하지 마세요. 나는 술을 마시지 않을 것이다.
Why?
왜?
The demo is now over.
이제 데모가 끝났습니다.
So what, we ourselves are not present.
그래서 우리 자신은 존재하지 않습니다.
I went to see it.
나는 그것을 보러 갔다.
This is a tiring process.
이것은 피곤한 과정입니다.
Anyway, I can't go tonight.
어쨌든 오늘 밤에는 갈 수 없어요.
Come on, why?
왜요?
- Can't go - Why?
- 갈 수 없어요 - 왜요?
Why?
왜?
- Stop - Why?
- 그만해 - 왜요?
Really, at that time , it made me want to cry.
정말 그땐 정말 울고 싶었어요.
that's right.
좋아요.
- I really understand - Yeah
- 정말 이해해요 - 네
But it still hurts.
하지만 여전히 아파요.
It's like they want to say "I got it, then go back."
마치 "알았어, 그럼 돌아가자" 라고 말하고 싶은 것과 같습니다 .
- They look like this every time... - I know.
- 매번 이런 표정인데... - 알아요.
I understand very well.
나는 아주 잘 이해합니다.
The boss also wants to drink.
사장님도 마시고 싶어하시네요.
For example, "I want to go drinking with you again."
예를 들어, "너랑 또 술 마시러 가고 싶어."
- Really? - Yes.
- 정말? - 예.
- If I get dumped, can I call my senior? - Yunjo, we are just supporting characters.
- 나 차버리면 선배한테 전화해도 돼? - 윤조 씨, 저희는 그냥 조연이에요.
- Congratulations on this auction .
- 이번 경매를 축하드립니다 .
- He chose... - Thank you very much.
- 그가 선택한 건... - 정말 고마워요.
Earth Communications has
어스커뮤니케이션즈는
"Marketing Team Leader Go Dong-kyun"
"마케팅팀장 고동균"
Who will introduce it?
누가 소개해줄까요?
Not prepared. Also, there is a lack of sincerity.
준비되지 않았습니다. 또한 성실성이 부족합니다.
In this way, I will trust you. How can you do this job?
이로써 나는 당신을 믿을 것입니다. 이 일을 어떻게 할 수 있나요?
- Senior must have really been drinking with me - He must be there
- 선배님은 정말 저랑 술을 마시고 계셨나봐요 - 거기 계셨나 봐요
You know what?
그거 알아?
- When that happens, maybe we should meet. - Yes
- 그럴 땐 만나야 할 것 같아요. - 예
The boss is lonely.
사장님은 외로워요.
- Seniors, you must drink with me. - Why haven't you called me recently?
- 선배님들, 저랑 꼭 마셔보세요 - 최근에는 왜 전화 안 받았어요?
- Ha - I'm very busy these days.
- 하 - 요즘 너무 바빠요.
-Are you so busy that you don't have time to call me? - bring it on.
- 너무 바빠서 나한테 전화할 시간도 없잖아? - 가져오세요.
- It's not like that... - The President
- 그런 건 아니고... - 대통령님
Yes
예
President, do you really have no feelings?
대통령님 정말 아무 감정 없으신가요?
That is,
그건,
I know.
알아요.
This is not EarthComm's fault.
이것은 EarthComm의 잘못이 아닙니다.
Yuncheng
윈청
but...
하지만...
I can't help but be jealous.
질투가 날 수밖에 없어요.
Why?
왜?
Why do I hate it so much?
나는 왜 그렇게 싫어합니까?
I'm already drunk.
나는 이미 취했다.
Yes, I'm drunk.
응, 나 취했어.
Because then I will...
그러면 내가 할 테니까...
excuse me
실례합니다
but the president
하지만 대통령은
I know.
알아요.
Oh I see
알겠어요
This circle...
이 원...
like this.
이와 같이.
You are still the seniors and juniors. EarthComm President Who can be here?
여러분은 아직도 선후배입니다. EarthComm 회장 누가 여기에 참석할 수 있나요?
- After everything I went through today - Yunjo
- 오늘 겪은 일을 마치고 - 윤조
but...
하지만...
everything...
모든 것...
everything about it
그것에 관한 모든 것
Is that a little too much?
좀 너무한가?
excuse me
실례합니다
What's wrong?
뭐가 문제 야?
Let's drink.
마시자.
"Jiemin"
"지민"
“Jaemin, you’ve received a new message.”
"재민아, 새 메시지를 받았어."
"Missed the call from Jae Min"
"재민이한테 전화가 안 왔어."
"say something"
"뭔가 말해봐"
"Jiemin"
"지민"
Answer the phone before I get angry. I was serious.
화내기 전에 전화를 받아라. 나는 진지했다.
Hey, I just sent you a message.
안녕하세요, 방금 메시지를 보냈습니다.
how do you say?
어떻게 말해요?
"Cloud Qiao Utopia"
"클라우드 치아오 유토피아"
What did you ask her to say?
그녀에게 무엇을 말해달라고 요청했나요?
"Answer the phone before I get mad. I'm telling the truth."
"화가 나기 전에 전화를 받아라. 나는 진실을 말하고 있다."
She probably wants to meet here.
그녀는 아마도 여기서 만나고 싶어할 것입니다.
It was like there was a war going on.
마치 전쟁이 벌어지고 있는 것 같았습니다.
Then I'll go home first.
그럼 나 먼저 집에 갈게.
this
이것
Wherever you go, you call her personally.
어디를 가든 그녀에게 개인적으로 전화합니다.
Listen, if you do something bad I confront her to end it all.
들어보세요, 당신이 나쁜 짓을 하면 나는 그녀에게 맞서서 모든 것을 끝내려고 합니다.
Stop putting it off, I understand.
그만 미루세요, 이해해요.
I'm going in.
나는 들어갈 것이다.
You are richer than your boss.
당신은 당신의 상사보다 더 부자입니다.
Well, bring me the most expensive wine. It's in the store.
그럼, 가장 비싼 와인을 가져오세요. 가게에 있어요.
Oh, okay, please wait a moment.
아, 알겠습니다. 잠시만 기다려 주십시오.
Hey, why are you walking around soaked?
야, 왜 흠뻑 젖어 돌아다니는 거야?
I don't have an umbrella.
나는 우산이 없습니다.
You can purchase it here.
여기에서 구매하실 수 있습니다.
Walking in the rain like this, my head is going to be bald.
이렇게 비를 맞으며 걷다 보면 머리가 대머리가 될 것 같아요.
not here
여기엔 없어
This is where things get hollow.
이것은 상황이 공허해지는 곳입니다.
Another plot...
또 다른 음모...
- Let's have a drink first - Yeah
- 우선 한잔하자 - 응
again?
다시?
- This is Yoo Jae Min - said
- 유재민입니다 - 라고요
Yoo Jae-min
유재민
Well, tell me.
글쎄, 말해봐.
This is Yoo Jae Min.
유재민입니다.
This guy is really bad.
이 사람 정말 나빠요.
Assistant Jiemin, please help me.
지민 보조님, 도와주세요.
Yes
예
Congratulations.
축하해요.
Thank you so much
매우 감사합니다
You belong there.
당신은 거기에 속해 있습니다.
- you know everything - well done
- 다 알잖아 - 잘했어
- good job today - you seem used to this
- 오늘 수고했어요 - 익숙해진 것 같군요
That's what makes me angry.
그것이 나를 화나게 하는 이유이다.
And the most angry
그리고 가장 화가 난 건
excuse me
실례합니다
Sorry, Yun Qiao.
미안해, 윤차오.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
This is understandable. Why couldn't he tell her first?
이것은 이해할 수 있습니다. 왜 그는 그녀에게 먼저 말할 수 없었습니까?
Is it right?
맞아?
I know.
알아요.
I just wanted to vent, that's all.
나는 단지 환기하고 싶었습니다. 그게 전부입니다.
Yes, let it out.
예, 내보내세요.
You can yell or cry all you want.
원하는 대로 소리를 지르거나 울어도 됩니다.
Stop it, you make me want to cry.
그만해요, 울고 싶게 만드네요.
But can I say one more thing?
그런데 한 가지만 더 말씀드려도 될까요?
no matter what the result is
결과가 어떻든 간에
I understand. How much do you plan to show?
이해합니다. 얼마나 보여줄 계획인가요?
It's really admirable.
정말 감탄스럽습니다.
Hehe, don’t you give people goosebumps when you say something like this? Am I the only one?
에헤헤 이런 말 하면 사람 소름 돋지 않나요? 제가 유일한가요?
In my heart, you are number one.
내 마음 속에는 당신이 1위입니다.
Shut up you idiot.
멍청 아 닥쳐.
hold hands and reconcile
손을 잡고 화해하다
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
You can act like a child.
어린아이처럼 행동해도 됩니다.
like this?
이와 같이?
Then we made up.
그런 다음 우리는 구성했습니다.
correct?
옳은?
Ha ha.
ㅋ.
Come, let's have a drink.
자, 한잔 하자.
collision
충돌
OK
좋아요
They say we get three chances in life.
인생에는 세 번의 기회가 있다고 하잖아요.
Who said?
누가 말했어?
I Ching
이칭
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
I really thought the opportunity was going to come
정말 기회가 올 줄 알았는데
But I was wrong.
그러나 나는 틀렸다.
Really bad.
정말 나쁘다.
But who will pay?
그런데 누가 지불할까요?
- Hey you idiot - Hey you
- 야 이 바보야 - 야 너
- Why? - You are the richest person in our group.
- 왜? - 당신은 우리 그룹에서 가장 부유한 사람입니다.
Didn't I tell you from the beginning , sir?
제가 처음부터 말하지 않았나요 선생님?
Have you told me already?
벌써 나한테 말했어?
- How much? - One million, eight hundred thousand won.
- 얼마나 많이? - 100만80만원.
1.8 million won...
180만원...
Hey, I'm a salaried employee.
안녕하세요, 저는 월급쟁이입니다.
Your salary is more than mine.
당신 월급이 나보다 많아요.
I'm also at a loss.
나도 헤매고 있어요.
Why do I need to make money? I got so much too.
왜 돈을 벌어야 합니까? 나도 너무 많이 얻었어요.
- Are you joking? - honestly.
- 농담하는 거야? - 솔직히.
Strategic General Manager Lin Zhixian
전략 총책임자 Lin Zhixian
The only daughter of the founder of Serong. The late Lim Chang-soo
세롱 창업주의 외동딸. 故 임창수씨
Affiliated to the Strategic Management Department
전략경영부 소속
There is a strategic planning department.
전략기획부서가 있습니다.
Human Resources Department
인사부
Legal Department
법무 부서
and our public relations department
그리고 우리 홍보부서
The truth is that the late Im Chang-soo
사실은 故 임창수씨가
Create a strategic management department to give your daughter more power
딸에게 더 많은 권한을 부여하기 위해 전략 관리 부서를 만드십시오
Because he is worried...
그 사람이 걱정하니까...
She may not be able to take over the company. when he died
그녀는 회사를 인수하지 못할 수도 있습니다. 그가 죽었을 때
"Vice President Zheng Jiuying of Shiyong Business Department "
"시용 사업부 부사장 Zheng Jiuying "
Yes, sir.
알겠습니다.
"Seyong, Sales Department, Kim Yeon-Soo, General Manager"
"세용 영업부 김연수 부장"
Why?
왜?
Because of Shi Yong’s driving force
시용의 원동력 때문에
This is the vice president of business. For example, is Zheng Jiuying still alive?
사업 부사장인데, 예를 들어 Zheng Jiuying이 아직 살아 있나요?
He is also the co-founder of Seyon. With the late Mr. Lim Chang-soo
세연의 공동 창업자이기도 하다. 故 임창수씨와 함께
The relationship between Vice President and General Manager?
부사장과 총책임자 의 관계 ?
OK
좋아요
Look outside.
밖을 바라보다.
《Seyuu》
《세용》
But if you look inside a little bit…
하지만 속을 조금만 들여다보면…
You will know.
넌 알게 될거야.
A fierce power struggle took place
치열한 권력다툼이 벌어졌다.
a while.
잠시.
Assistant Jaemin, what do you think?
재민보좌관님, 어떻게 생각하시나요?
Where are you?
어디세요?
Ha, are you in the conference room?
하, 지금 회의실에 있나요?
Ha, can't you see me?
하, 나 안 보여?
Hey, here it is.
안녕하세요. 여기 있습니다.
what are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
What is the manager doing with the intern?
매니저는 인턴을 데리고 무엇을 하고 있나요?
Summary of the situation in the Shi Yong government . Let them listen.
시영정부 상황 요약 . 들어보게 하라.
- Or historical drama introduction - Bingo
- 혹은 사극 소개 - 빙고
Assistant Jaemin, what's wrong?
재민보좌관, 무슨 일이에요?
Oh, Director Jon from the cosmetics department. I want to talk to you about the auction...
아, 화장품 부서 존 국장님. 경매에 관해 이야기하고 싶습니다.
Now Jaemin's assistant. You have a responsibility, don't you?
이제 재민의 어시스턴트 책임을 져야겠죠?
take over from me
나에게서 인계받아
OK
좋아요
He's so cool.
그는 정말 멋지다.
He's going to ask for help again, right?
그 사람이 다시 도움을 요청할 거예요, 그렇죠?
I had no idea I was coming to the meeting today.
오늘 회의에 올 줄은 몰랐어요.
Less than 49 days.
49일 미만입니다.
This is not the Joseon era at all.
지금은 전혀 조선시대가 아니다.
yes...
예...
It's not like you have to sit by the grave for 49 days.
49일 동안 무덤 곁에 앉아 있어야 하는 것은 아닙니다 .
This is real.
이것은 진짜입니다.
I thought you wanted me to stay because I had something else to tell you.
나는 당신에게 할 말이 더 있기 때문에 당신이 내가 머물기를 원한다고 생각했습니다 .
be patient.
인내심을 가지십시오.
Be patient and let's work together.
인내심을 갖고 함께 일합시다.
Thanks
감사해요
She probably doesn't know yet. Because there’s a lot to think about.
그녀는 아마 아직 모르고 있을 것이다. 생각할 것이 많기 때문입니다.
There's bad news.
나쁜 소식이 있어요.
Just like the public relations aspect, it's not going to be very effective.
홍보 측면과 마찬가지로 그다지 효과적이지 않을 것입니다.
I'm considering moving them. Affiliated to the business department
옮기는 것을 고려 중이에요. 사업부 소속
I'll handle it myself.
내가 직접 처리하겠습니다.
No
아니요
OK
좋아요
"General Manager of Strategy Department Lin Zhixian"
"전략부 총책임자 Lin Zhixian"
"Daguo Daily"
"대궈일보"
"Bribery auction to replace Seyon's manufacturer?"
" 세연의 제조사를 대체하기 위한 뇌물경매?"
The person in charge of the public relations department was called.
홍보부서 담당자가 호출되었습니다.
Yes
예
"Planning Department"
"계획 부서"
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
We've been discussing this issue for some time.
우리는 이 문제를 한동안 논의해 왔습니다.
And the plan we chose...
그리고 우리가 선택한 플랜은...
That's the plan.
그게 계획이에요.
"Celtics Online and Offline Campaign Plan PR Joa"
"셀틱스 온라인 및 오프라인 캠페인 기획 PR 조아"
boss
사장
I know we should choose EarthComm.
나는 우리가 EarthComm을 선택해야 한다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
But Earth Communications You can use this plan instead.
하지만 Earth Communications 대신 이 계획을 사용할 수 있습니다.
I've done this before.
나는 전에 이것을 해본 적이 있습니다.
Since creative media strategy...
창의적인 미디어 전략 이후...
This is better.
이게 낫다.
"Celtics Online and Offline Campaign Plan PR Joa"
"셀틱스 온라인 및 오프라인 캠페인 기획 PR 조아"
This really happened.
이런 일이 실제로 일어났습니다.
But the other company isn't Earth Communications.
하지만 다른 회사는 Earth Communications가 아닙니다.
But it used to be.
하지만 예전에는 그랬습니다.
What about regulations?
규정은 어떻습니까?
There are no rules.
규칙이 없습니다.
Who do you think the company didn't win the bid for this job?
회사가 이 일에 대한 입찰에서 낙찰받지 못한 사람 이 누구 라고 생각합니까 ?
Are they going to say, "You don't have to pay us. Steal our ideas"?
그들은 "당신은 우리에게 돈을 지불할 필요가 없습니다. 우리의 아이디어를 훔칠 필요가 없습니다"라고 말할 것입니까 ?
They sell plans at a fair price, right?
그들은 공정한 가격에 플랜을 판매합니다. 그렇죠?
Let EarthComm take care of it.
EarthComm이 처리해 드리겠습니다.
Whether to pay or not is their own business.
지불할지 여부는 각자의 문제입니다.
Anyway, let's proceed as planned. PR Joa.
어쨌든 계획대로 진행하자. 홍보 조아.
Boss Song must be frightened.
송사장은 겁을 먹었나 봐요.
Gioia’s PR plan?
지오이아의 홍보 계획은요?
I didn't expect this at all.
나는 이것을 전혀 기대하지 않았습니다.
No, say no.
아니, 아니오라고 말하세요.
Cosmetics Sales Team Leader A team, right?
화장품영업팀장 A팀이죠?
Yes
예
Only a child would do such a thing.
그런 일은 어린아이만이 할 수 있다.
Where are you from?
어디서 오셨나요?
I think I'll use this plan. Can I throw it away?
나는 이 계획을 사용할 것 같아요. 버릴 수 있나요?
But PR Joa has a better plan...
하지만 PR Joa에게는 더 나은 계획이 있습니다 ...
damn it.
젠장.
Don't answer the phone during working hours?
근무시간에 전화를 안받으시나요?
Yoo Jae-min
유재민
Will you go with him too?
너도 그 사람이랑 같이 갈래?
gentlemen...
신사...
Yes, Manager Kim.
네, 김 과장님.
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Yes, I'm on my way.
네, 지금 가는 중이에요.
Yes
예
Come, follow me.
나를 따라와.
"General Manager of Strategy Department"
"전략부장"
In summary...
요약하자면...
You take the money and throw it over your head. And let it come back to haunt us?
당신은 돈을 가져다가 머리 위로 던집니다. 그리고 그것이 다시 우리를 괴롭히게 놔두시겠습니까?
It is not.
그렇지 않습니다.
They will be releasing new information soon. Come fix the news and...
그들은 곧 새로운 정보를 공개할 예정입니다. 와서 뉴스를 고치고...
No one watches the news.
뉴스를 보는 사람은 아무도 없습니다.
read.
읽다.
The Vice President will definitely read it.
부통령님이 꼭 읽어보실 겁니다.
Is there nothing?
아무것도 없나요?
Let's break the big news about the good things Seyong is doing.
세용이가 하는 좋은 일들에 대한 빅뉴스를 전해보자 .
Our media-loving Vice President would be delighted.
미디어를 사랑하는 우리 부사장님도 기뻐하실 겁니다.
- Boss Song - Yes.
- 송사장님 - 네.
What's wrong with this?
이게 무슨 문제야?
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
I'll try to think about it.
나는 그것에 대해 생각하려고 노력할 것입니다.
Who are you?
누구세요?
Assistant Manager Liu Jae-min from Public Relations Team 2
홍보2팀 류재민 대리
Yoo Jae-min
유재민
Someone who writes a good manifesto?
좋은 선언문을 쓰는 사람?
I'm surprised you remember this.
당신이 이것을 기억하고 있다는 게 놀랍습니다.
The general manager is really smart.
총지배인은 정말 똑똑합니다.
What about Ryu's assistant?
류의 어시스턴트는 어떻습니까?
Can you come up with great ideas quickly?
좋은 아이디어가 빨리 떠오르나요?
drowning in news about our abuse of power
우리의 권력 남용에 대한 뉴스 에 빠져들다
What other companies do we don’t do.
다른 회사에서는 우리가 하지 않는 일을 합니다.
But we shouldn't imitate them.
그러나 우리는 그들을 모방해서는 안 됩니다.
What makes us look good and different?
무엇이 우리를 멋지고 다르게 보이게 만드는가?
Employment without discrimination
차별 없는 고용
Non-discriminatory employment?
차별 없는 고용?
I hear this sound every day.
나는 매일 이 소리를 듣습니다.
Are you saying there is discrimination?
차별이 있다는 말씀이신가요?
This is something every company does. Except us.
이건 회사마다 하는 일이에요. 우리만 빼고요.
Regarding hiring only experienced people I think giving employees...
경력자만 채용하는 것에 관해서 는 직원들에게...
Choose the people you want to work with. It's not like the others.
함께 일하고 싶은 사람들을 선택하세요. 다른 사람들과는 다릅니다.
OK
좋아요
be prepared
준비하다
- Next executive meeting - Yes.
- 다음 임원회의 - 네.
Then send out a press release and let the media be everywhere except the "Da Guo Daily".
그런 다음 보도 자료를 발송 하고 "Da Guo Daily"를 제외한 모든 곳에 언론을 노출시키십시오.
But General Manager , if we do this, the consequences...
그런데 단장님 , 이렇게 하면 결과가...
Then withdraw the ad.
그런 다음 광고를 철회하세요.
Don't let it trample you. Take action first.
그것이 당신을 짓밟게 두지 마십시오. 먼저 조치를 취하십시오.
you can go now.
이제 가셔도 됩니다.
-I can go. -Yes.
- 갈 수 있어요 - 네
This is the latest news from Mr. Goo Eui-jung.
구의정씨의 최신 소식입니다.
Many Korean companies invited her to participate in this event.
많은 한국 기업들이 그녀를 이번 행사에 초대했습니다.
But she refused.
그러나 그녀는 거절했습니다.
She's your college friend. She might accept...
그 사람은 네 대학 친구야. 그 사람이 받아들일 수도 있겠네요...
We hate each other.
우리는 서로를 싫어합니다.
There is a big debate about a man.
남자에 관해 큰 논쟁이 있습니다.
I haven't spoken to her in over 20 years.
나는 20년 넘게 그녀와 이야기를 나누지 않았습니다.
"2022 Influential Female Leaders Public Relations Consultant Goo Eui-jung"
"2022 영향력 있는 여성리더 홍보컨설턴트 구의정"
"manage"
"관리하다"
“Jenny Gu’s American Dream is real.”
“Jenny Gu의 아메리칸 드림은 현실입니다.”
- Mr. President - Yeah.
- 대통령 각하 - 네.
chirchan's children
치르찬의 아이들
- Here we come - Are you hungry?
- 간다 - 배고프니?
so cute.
너무 귀엽다.
She died, just like her mother.
그녀는 어머니처럼 죽었습니다.
- Very similar - Yes
- 매우 유사함 - 예
Look at those chubby cheeks.
저 통통한 볼을 보세요.
- So cute. - Oh my god, so beautiful.
- 너무 귀여워요 - 맙소사, 너무 아름다워요
but...
하지만...
From now on, Li Zhezhang's life will be difficult.
이제부터 Li Zhezhang의 삶은 어려울 것입니다.
Raising a child alone is difficult these days. Just twins
요즘 혼자 아이를 키우는 것은 어렵습니다. 그냥 쌍둥이야
That's it.
그게 다야.
And, with no one to help her, the work was really hard.
그리고 그녀를 도와줄 사람이 아무도 없어서 그 일은 정말 힘들었습니다.
I need to make a lot of money.
돈을 많이 벌어야 해요.
It's easy to say.
말하기는 쉽습니다.
This is real.
이것은 진짜입니다.
I have more responsibility to take care of myself.
나 자신을 돌보는 데 더 많은 책임이 있습니다.
Damn it
젠장
- You had a drink. - Have a good meal.
- 술을 마셨어요. - 맛있게 드세요.
- Thank you, good bye.
- 고마워요, 안녕히 계세요.
welcome.
환영.
- Hello - I will definitely wait.
- 안녕하세요 - 꼭 기다리겠습니다.
Is this your favorite bakery?
여기가 당신이 가장 좋아하는 빵집인가요?
Check it out, it's very popular.
확인해 보세요. 매우 인기가 많습니다.
The bread wasn't very tasty , but it was very popular.
빵은 별로 맛없었지만 인기가 많았어요.
How did I get interested?
나는 어떻게 관심을 가지게 되었나요?
- Buy it and take it home? - but...
- 사서 집에 가져갈까? - 하지만...
I need to find something to seduce them.
그들을 유혹할 뭔가를 찾아야 해요.
she thinks...
그녀는 생각한다...
Do they have the money to promote the store?
매장을 홍보할 돈이 있나요?
Well, if the idea is good and not much money...
뭐, 아이디어가 좋고 돈이 별로 없다면...
- Mr. President - Yeah.
- 대통령 각하 - 네.
I will be looking for new clients this time.
이번에는 새로운 고객을 찾아보겠습니다.
Oh, did you get a sales job?
아, 영업직 구하셨나요?
So thank you very much.
정말 감사합니다.
But I'm still ashamed
하지만 난 아직도 부끄러워
Don't be shy.
부끄러워하지 마세요.
I'll take another look here. Please feel free to come.
여기서 한 번 더 살펴보겠습니다. 부담 없이 오시기 바랍니다.
Yes, I'll throw it away for you.
응, 버릴게.
Work hard to find new customers.
새로운 고객을 찾기 위해 열심히 노력하세요.
Please, I'm so confused.
제발, 너무 혼란스러워요.
But I like it.
그러나 나는 그것이 좋다.
excuse me
실례합니다
I wonder why it's so loud?
왜 이렇게 시끄러운지 궁금합니다.
This is protein bread.
단백질빵이에요.
I know, but it's not the only one. This is where I make my protein bread.
알아요. 하지만 그것만이 유일한 것은 아닙니다. 이곳은 제가 단백질 빵을 만드는 곳입니다.
They only sell limited quantities.
한정수량만 판매합니다.
And it tastes better. There are other types of protein bread
그리고 맛이 더 좋습니다. 다른 종류의 단백질빵도 있어요
Here, let us gather together.
여기, 함께 모이자.
- Okay - Hey, shut up.
- 알았어 - 이봐, 닥쳐.
- Where are you? - OK.
- 어디세요? - 좋아요.
Hey, watch my back, protect me.
야, 내 뒤를 조심해, 나를 지켜줘
Ok, I see.
그래 알았어.
this
이것
Wait here.
여기서 기다리세요.
damn it!
젠장!
Hey, I told you to watch your back.
야, 내가 허리 조심하라고 했잖아.
Why...
왜...
- I can't shoot. - Are you kidding me? Hold.
- 총을 쏠 수가 없어요 - 농담하는 건가요? 잡고 있다.
Eun-soo, what are you doing?
은수 씨, 뭐 해요?
- You have no sense of direction - Where to go?
- 방향 감각이 없군요 . - 어디로 가야 할까요?
Here, load the bullets.
여기에 총알을 장전하세요.
- Hey , what are you doing?
- 헤이 너 뭐하는거야?
- Hey, take it. - Damn, take it.
- 이봐, 받아 - 젠장, 가져가
- Yes - That's great.
- 네 - 좋아요.
- Great - What, why are you here?
- 좋아요 - 뭐야, 왜 여기 있어?
It's been a while.
오랜만이야.
WHO？
WHO?
Haizu's sister.
하이즈의 여동생.
nice to meet
만나서 반가워요
Hey, why did you say my sister is dead?
야, 왜 내 여동생이 죽었다고 했어?
Is it right?
맞아?
When will I die?
나는 언제 죽을 것인가?
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
continue.
계속하다.
Is it a good idea to join the army after graduation?
졸업 후 군대에 가는 것이 좋은 생각인가요?
I found the right way here.
나는 여기서 올바른 길을 찾았습니다.
No
아니요
I heard that high school students like it very much.
고등학생들이 아주 좋아한다고 들었습니다.
Especially a woman like her.
특히 그녀 같은 여자는요.
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
protein bread
단백질 빵
Yes, like a kid in school. We will eat a lot.
그래요, 학교에 다니는 어린아이처럼요. 우리는 많이 먹을 것이다.
I saw that it can help you lose weight.
체중 감량에 도움이 될 수 있다고 봤습니다.
Do high school students lose a lot of weight?
고등학생은 살이 많이 빠지나요?
you're old.
당신은 늙었어요.
- Hey, protein bread - cool, awesome.
- 안녕, 단백질 빵 - 정말 멋지다.
- Come, have a good meal - Yeah
- 와서 밥 잘 먹어 - 응
- Awesome. Thank you. - Very delicious.
- 최고예요, 고마워요 - 아주 맛있어요.
this is delicious.
이거 맛있다.
- Awesome - Delicious
- 굉장해요 - 맛있어요
Can it help you lose weight?
체중 감량에 도움이 될까요?
- It's really delicious. - It's delicious.
- 정말 맛있어요 - 맛있어요
Is it tasty?
맛있나요?
very soft
매우 부드러운
- Is this protein bread? - delicious.
- 이게 단백질빵인가요? - 맛있는.
- Yes - try it.
- 네 - 한번 해보세요.
- Very delicious
- 아주 맛있어요
Manager Jin I just had a chat with Manager Jin.
진 과장 방금 진과장님과 이야기를 나눴습니다.
General Manager Kim Yeon- soo From the sales department?
김연수 부장 영업부서요?
We must follow the plan. PR Joa
우리는 그 계획을 따라야 합니다. PR 조아
Call EarthComm's Seo Dong Hoon and tell him to proceed as planned.
어스컴 서동훈에게 전화해서 계획대로 진행하라고 하세요.
That Jon Da Jeong girl, I...
그 존다정 여자, 난...
Then come on, say you understand me.
그럼 어서, 내 말을 이해한다고 말해주세요.
I don’t want to believe I’m putting it off. The general manager is also involved.
나는 그것을 미루고 있다고 믿고 싶지 않습니다. 총책임자도 참여합니다.
Listen, tell him to start making new plans.
들어봐, 그에게 새로운 계획을 세우라고 말해줘.
It looks like it was their idea.
그들의 생각이었던 것 같습니다.
What
무엇
Nothing.
아무것도 아님.
"Celtics Online and Offline Campaign Plan PR Joa"
"셀틱스 온라인 및 오프라인 캠페인 기획 PR 조아"
Yes, I understand.
네 이해했습니다.
what are you planning to do?
당신은 무엇을 할 계획입니까?
sorry.
죄송합니다.
I'm not laughing at you.
나는 당신을 비웃는 것이 아닙니다.
hair...
머리카락...
I'll handle it myself.
내가 직접 처리하겠습니다.
《Seyuu》
《세용》
"Angus Bread"
"앵거스 브레드"
You two were just baking. And running a store leaves little time.
너희 둘은 방금 빵을 굽고 있었어. 그리고 매장을 운영하는 데에는 시간이 거의 남지 않습니다.
We will take care of your social media accounts.
귀하의 소셜 미디어 계정을 관리해 드리겠습니다.
We're going to build absolutely an online store.
우리는 완전한 온라인 상점을 구축할 것입니다 .
You may be popular among teenagers
당신은 십대들에게 인기가 있을 수도 있습니다
You have to take this seriously.
이것을 진지하게 받아들여야 합니다.
Now this market...
지금 이 시장은...
At the moment we don't have enough money to promote it.
현재로서는 홍보할 자금이 충분하지 않습니다.
We will discuss payment terms later. Is it good after sales increase?
나중에 지불 조건에 대해 논의하겠습니다. 매출이 오르면 좋은 걸까요?
very good.
매우 좋은.
Yes
예
here it is.
여기있어.
If you try it...
시도해 보면 ...
"Angus Bread"
"앵거스 브레드"
“Angus bread #protein bar #protein cake”
“앵거스빵 #프로틴바 #프로틴케이크”
"Blind Test Wheel"
"블라인드 테스트 휠"
"Chairman Xu Dongxun, evaluate based on ability."
"서동순 회장님, 능력으로 평가해주세요."
"Celtics Online and Offline Campaign Plan PR Joa"
"셀틱스 온라인 및 오프라인 캠페인 기획 PR 조아"
"Angus Bread"
"앵거스 브레드"
Hello everyone
여러분, 안녕하세요
It's Hai Qiao.
하이차오입니다.
This is a bakery called Angs Bread. I will review their products...
앙스브레드(Angs Bread)라는 빵집이에요. 나는 그들의 제품을 검토 할 것입니다 ...
Okay, here...
알았어, 여기...
-Hello boss. ​​-Hello.
- 안녕하세요 사장님. ​​-안녕하세요.
Hello
안녕하세요
I just saw something super cute.
방금 엄청 귀여운 걸 봤어요.
so cute.
너무 귀엽다.
I'm finally going to try their bread, let's go.
드디어 그 빵을 먹어보러 가보겠습니다 .
This is protein bread.
단백질빵이에요.
Even if you eat it, you won't gain weight.
먹어도 살이 찌지 않습니다.
Mae Haek is delicious.
매핵 맛있어요.
What's this? Very tasty.
이건 뭐죠? 아주 맛있는.
"Have you ever tried Angus bread? The protein bread is delicious."
"앵거스 빵을 먹어본 적 있나요? 단백질 빵이 맛있어요."
- It's really good. - Very delicious.
- 정말 맛있어요 - 아주 맛있어요
- But Tan - So cute.
- 그런데 탄 - 너무 귀여워요.
So cute, so cute, the logo is adorable.
너무 귀엽고 귀엽고 로고도 귀엽네요.
This is a donut that won't make you fat.
살이 찌지 않는 도넛이에요.
“#honestreview#donutreview#taste”
“#솔직한리뷰#도넛리뷰#맛”
Normally I don't eat bread. But I like this.
평소에는 빵을 잘 안 먹어요. 하지만 나는 이것을 좋아한다.
This is protein bread. Eat without feeling guilty.
단백질빵이에요. 죄책감 없이 먹습니다.
"Nosab, it's a nice day today. Come talk to us."
"노삽, 오늘은 좋은 날이야. 와서 얘기 좀 하자."
"Ang Bread, have you heard of it? It's so popular, go and buy it."
"앙브레드, 들어보셨나요? 인기가 너무 많으니 가서 사보세요."
“Eat protein bread when you’re tired.”
"피곤할 땐 단백질빵을 먹어라"
The chocolate flavor is very rich.
초코맛이 아주 풍부해요.
Is it delicious?
맛있어?
"Hai Zuyu, have you ever eaten this?"
"하이쥬위, 이거 먹어본 적 있어요?"
Have you eaten?
식사하셨나요?
"Angus Bread"
"앵거스 브레드"
"Here's the snack you asked for."
"여기 당신이 요청한 간식이 있습니다."
"You have to carry it with you forever."
"영원히 가지고 다녀야 해요."
“The bread in this store is delicious.”
“이 가게 빵이 맛있어요.”
"Order payment date"
"주문결제일"
"President"
"대통령"
president
대통령
Um?
음?
Come quickly.
빨리 오세요.
Damn, what?
젠장, 뭐?
How is this going?
어떻게 되어가나요?
look at this.
이거 봐요.
"Order, payment, refund, cancellation, return"
"주문,결제,환불, 취소,반품"
"Net balance in the last 7 days: 23,493,500 won"
"지난 7일 순잔액: 23,493,500원"
crazy
미친
Sales surged.
매출이 급증했습니다.
Unbelievable, right?
믿을 수 없지, 그렇지?
Yes, it is rising.
예, 상승하고 있습니다.
This is Yun Qiao.
윤차오입니다.
I did it.
내가 해냈어.
It's all over.
모든 끝났어.
Oh my lucky star mom is so talented.
아, 나의 행운의 별 엄마는 정말 재능이 있어요.
Wow, awesome.
대단해.
"Daguo Daily"
"대궈일보"
"If you can't stop eating bread, then treat yourself to it. 'Protein Bread'"
"빵을 멈출 수 없다면, 빵 을 먹어보세요. '단백질 빵'"
"'Protein bread' is made with protein powder..."
"'단백질 빵'은 단백질 가루로 만든다…"
"Daeguk Daily Reporter Choi Hye-young"
"대국일보 최혜영 기자"
station...
역...
Hey, you workaholic.
이봐, 너 워커홀릭이구나.
Are you OK? Are you happy and excited?
괜찮으세요? 당신은 행복하고 흥분됩니까?
you do not know. I'm in heaven.
넌 몰라. 저는 천국에 있습니다.
"Daodong Paradise"
"다오동 파라다이스"
- Ha - Starry Sky Paradise...
- 하 - 별이 빛나는 하늘의 천국...
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Anyway, thanks for the message.
어쨌든 메시지 주셔서 감사합니다.
When did you give it to Reporter Choi?
최기자한테는 언제 주셨나요?
I'm pretty good at it, right?
나 꽤 잘하는 것 맞지?
She couldn't have asked for a better friend.
그녀는 더 나은 친구를 요구할 수 없었습니다.
She is addicted to me.
그녀는 나에게 중독되어 있습니다.
Her income is much less than mine.
그녀의 수입은 나보다 훨씬 적습니다.
But you still owe me.
하지만 당신은 나에게 아직 빚을 지고 있어요.
Why does it sound like this?
왜 이런 소리가 나나요?
Don't change the subject.
주제를 바꾸지 마세요.
So disgusting
너무 역겨워
"Yun Qiao"
"윤차오"
Yes, said Yoo Jae-min.
네, 유재민이 말했습니다.
"Recruiting experienced staff"
"경력직원을 모집합니다"
“Sifting through closed data by lower-level employees”
“ 하급 직원의 비공개 데이터 선별 ”
"No qualifications specified . No personal relationships were exploited."
"자격이 명시되지 않았습니다 . 개인적인 관계가 이용되지 않았습니다."
"Employees choose their colleagues..."
"직원이 동료를 선택한다…"
When posting, emphasize the word "grassroots employees"
게시할 때 '풀뿌리 직원' 이라는 단어를 강조하세요.
And emphasize "only use experience"
그리고 "경험만을 사용하라"를 강조하세요
Yes
예
This is indeed the case and must be clearly stated. This is a temporary position
이는 실제로 사실이며 명확하게 명시되어야 합니다. 임시직입니다
I thought this was a permanent position.
나는 이것이 정규직이라고 생각했습니다.
If it was so easy to get a permanent position, why open applications?
정규직을 구하는 것이 그렇게 쉬웠다면 왜 지원서를 제출해야 합니까?
if they do a good job
그들이 일을 잘한다면
In two years, I might be hired.
2년 뒤에는 채용될 수도 있어요.
It's so hard to prove yourself in Seiyong .
세이용에서는 자신을 증명하는 것이 너무 어렵습니다 .
Why
왜
I’m afraid people won’t apply. Because it's a temporary position?
사람들이 신청하지 않을까 걱정이에요. 임시직이라서?
No, people must be swarming like bees.
아니, 사람들이 벌떼처럼 모여들고 있는 모양이다.
Korea is simply hell on earth.
한국은 그야말로 지옥이다.
Yes, that's what I'm saying.
예, 그게 제가 말하는 것입니다.
You can leave now.
지금 떠나셔도 됩니다.
Jia Min is probably the only one. Within our PR team, our second team
아마도 지아민이 유일할 것이다. 우리 PR팀 중 두 번째 팀은
who actually works here
실제로 여기서 일하는 사람
real
진짜
There is another me.
또 다른 내가 있습니다.
See you tomorrow.
내일 봐요.
are you happy?
행복하니?
Are you happy that you are good at spending time alone?
혼자 시간을 잘 보낼 수 있어서 행복한가요?
Well, this is the team’s ace in the hole.
글쎄요, 이것이 팀의 에이스입니다.
Believe it.
믿으세요.
"No qualifications specified. Just experience required."
"지정된 자격은 없습니다. 경험만 있으면 됩니다."
"Lower-level staff, will you filter and close this information?"
"하급 직원 여러분, 이 정보를 필터링하고 닫으시겠습니까?"
"They are accepting applications. In terms of work ability"
"지원서를 받고 있습니다. 업무 능력면에서"
"Do not view data, do not specify attributes"
"데이터를 보지 말고 속성을 지정하지 마십시오"
"I applied for this round, but no information was disclosed. Let's go to Xie Yong's house."
"이번 라운드에 지원했는데 정보가 공개되지 않았어요. 시용 씨 집으로 가자."
"Recruitment of experienced employees 2022 special round"
"2022년 특별 라운드 경력사원 채용 "
“No qualifications specified, only work experience.”
“자격은 따로 정해져 있지 않고 경력만 있어요.”
"feature"
"특징"
"Workspace"
"작업 공간"
"Education, language proficiency, gender, age: not specified"
"학력, 어학능력, 성별, 나이 : 미지정"
The bus is coming.
버스가 오고 있어요.
"Jaemin received new news."
"재민이가 새로운 소식을 들었어요."
"Shiyong Official Website"
"시용 공식 홈페이지"
excuse me
실례합니다
"Recruitment of experienced employees 2022 special round"
"2022년 특별 라운드 경력사원 채용 "
“No qualifications specified, only work experience.”
“자격은 따로 정해져 있지 않고 경력만 있어요.”
- Thank you - Yeah
- 고마워요 - 네
Thanks
감사해요
Yes, bye.
응 안녕.
is it here?
여기야?
Yes, Building 103.
네, 103빌딩입니다.
Building 103, yes.
103빌딩 그렇죠.
- is that so? - Come on, let's go.
- 그렇습니까? - 자, 가자.
- Oh my God
- 맙소사
- No, I'm dead. - Be careful.
- 아니, 난 죽었어 - 조심하세요
Oh, it's going to hurt.
아, 아플 것 같아요.
deadly
죽음
excuse me
실례합니다
- It's okay - Ms. Huajia
- 괜찮아 - 화지아 씨
feels good.
좋은 느낌.
Oh, Mr. Yunqiao.
아, 윤차오 씨.
-This is my mom -ha
- 이분은 우리 엄마예요 -하
I will take you there myself. You go.
내가 직접 거기까지 데려다줄게.
Bro, I'm sorry.
형, 미안해요.
Wait, Hua...
잠깐, 후아...
deadly
죽음
Damn it
젠장
Where can I find such a man?
그런 남자를 어디서 찾을 수 있나요?
I still have stuff, right?
아직 물건이 있어요, 그렇죠?
Go bake with those people. To prove it?
그 사람들과 함께 빵을 구워보세요. 그것을 증명하기 위해?
I still have stuff.
아직 물건이 있어요.
Miss Huajia
미스 화지아
As for you, no.
당신은 그렇지 않습니다.
Hey, why have you never dated anyone else?
야, 왜 다른 사람이랑 데이트한 적 없어?
real
진짜
How would you feel if your daughter went to Seyong to work ?
딸이 세용이한테 일하러 간다면 어떤 기분일까요 ?
You don't like men?
당신은 남자를 좋아하지 않습니까?
Women, if you like women, go find them.
여자들이여, 여자를 좋아한다면 가서 찾아보세요.
I ask you how you feel. If I go to work in Seyong
기분이 어떤지 묻습니다. 내가 세용에 출근하면
So are you bored?
그래서 지루해요?
Hello
안녕하세요
Wow!
우와!
Look for
찾다
how do you say?
어떻게 말해요?
What do you think I should do?
내가 어떻게 해야 한다고 생각하세요?
Should I say no and no longer work with Se Yong?
거절 하고 더 이상 세용이랑 일하지 말아야 할까요 ?
damn it.
젠장.
There is a refrigerator outside.
밖에 냉장고가 있어요.
There's soju in it.
소주도 들어있어요
- Go get it. - Senior
- 가서 가져오세요. - 상위
So what do you want to do?
그럼 당신은 무엇을 하고 싶나요?
So please tell me what I should do.
그러니 제가 무엇을 해야 하는지 말씀해 주십시오.
Then I'll do it.
그럼 내가 할게요.
I don't know anything else.
나는 다른 것을 모른다.
Yes
예
Take Manager Park as an example.
박 감독을 예로 들어보자.
These are all Yun Qiao's masterpiece.
이것들은 모두 Yun Qiao의 걸작입니다.
What is most important to the company?
회사에 가장 중요한 것은 무엇입니까?
sustainable development
지속 가능한 개발
So what makes a company sustainable?
그렇다면 기업을 지속가능하게 만드는 것은 무엇일까?
First, a company must have a market.
첫째, 기업에는 시장이 있어야 한다.
Selling products and services
제품 및 서비스 판매
Secondly, we must know what is the financial status of the company?
둘째, 회사의 재무상태가 어떠한지 알아야 합니다 .
Will make business decisions that are always correct
항상 올바른 비즈니스 결정을 내릴 것입니다.
last but not least
마지막으로 중요한 것은
The world must still exist.
세상은 여전히 ​​존재해야 합니다.
This is the reason for "SPP".
이것이 "SPP"의 이유입니다.
It stands for environment, society and governance.
이는 환경(Environment), 사회(Society), 거버넌스(Governance)를 의미합니다 .
This is important nowadays.
요즘엔 이게 중요해요.
Because of this, we must pay attention to...
그렇기 때문에 우리는 주의를 기울여야 합니다...
All factors This has a greater impact on SPP.
모든 요인 이는 SPP에 더 큰 영향을 미칩니다.
Make our business sustainable
우리의 사업을 지속 가능하게 만드세요
not just for ourselves
우리 자신만을 위해서가 아니라
but...
하지만...
for the future of this world
이 세상의 미래를 위해
and our descendants
그리고 우리 후손들
Thanks
감사해요
Miss
놓치다
"New York"
"뉴욕"
You don't have to call the lady. When the two of us are together it's okay.
그 여자에게 전화할 필요는 없어요. 둘이 같이 있으면 괜찮아요.
They sent me because I knew we were good friends.
우리가 좋은 친구라는 것을 알았기 때문에 그들은 나를 보냈습니다 .
Linda
린다
Thank you for your suggestion, but...
제안은 감사합니다만...
Is there a "but"?
"그러나"가 있습니까?
I don't want to hear it anymore.
더 이상 듣고 싶지 않아요.
I stopped playing politics for a while.
한동안 정치를 그만두었습니다.
There's no big reason for this.
여기에는 큰 이유가 없습니다.
People still want Jenny.
사람들은 여전히 ​​제니를 원해요.
I failed too.
나도 실패했다.
And it was successful too.
그리고 그것도 성공했어요.
are you sure?
확실합니까?
Yes
예
OK
좋아요
I can't be convinced if Jenny is sure.
Jenny가 확신한다면 나는 확신할 수 없습니다.
Now working as a consultant How are you?
지금은 컨설턴트로 일하고 계시죠?
Excellent...
훌륭한...
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Jenny
제니
Why don't you take a break?
좀 쉬는 게 어때?
You look very tired.
당신은 매우 피곤해 보입니다.
you know me.
당신은 나를 알고 있습니다.
This is enough to charge your energy up to 100%.
이는 에너지를 100%까지 충전하기에 충분합니다.
My mission must have failed.
내 임무는 실패한 게 틀림없어.
Hey Jenny.
안녕, 제니.
The coffee is delicious.
커피는 맛있습니다.
What brand is it?
어떤 브랜드인가요?
I think I told your secretary not to come.
내가 당신 비서한테 오지 말라고 말한 것 같아요.
I don't see any messages being received.
수신된 메시지가 표시되지 않습니다.
Got it, but didn't pay much attention to it.
알았지만 크게 신경쓰지는 않았습니다.
- So - it hasn't changed at all.
- 그러니까 - 전혀 변하지 않았네요.
Do what you want as usual.
평소처럼 원하는 대로 하세요.
That's my charm.
그게 내 매력이야.
I want you to help me.
당신이 나를 도와줬으면 좋겠어.
I?
나?
Why should I help?
왜 도와야 합니까?
China Association for Science and Technology
중국과학기술협회
If you accept this job I will give you everything you want
당신이 이 일을 받아들이면 당신이 원하는 모든 것을 주겠다.
If you think I'd take a job for the money...
내가 돈 때문에 일을 할 거라고 생각한다면…
Can you make me kneel down?
나를 무릎꿇게 해줄 수 있나요?
I need you more than anyone right now.
지금 누구보다 당신이 필요해요.
"Utopia"
"유토피아"
I don’t know if Yin Zu applied. Didn't get any news at all.
Yin Zu가 지원했는지는 모르겠습니다. 전혀 소식을 듣지 못했습니다.
She probably won't tell. Is it because I'm afraid of being embarrassed?
그녀는 아마 말하지 않을 것입니다. 부끄러워질까 봐 두려워서일까?
this is possible.
이것은 가능하다.
But I bet she applied for 10,000 won.
그런데 그 사람이 10,000원을 신청했을 것 같아요.
Me too. I bet she applied for 20,000 won.
저도요. 아마 2만원을 신청했을 거에요.
Are you kidding me? You have to stab the other person.
농담하는 거야? 상대방을 찔러야 합니다.
you are still working?
아직도 일하고 ​​있어?
Actually I said
사실 내가 말했지
They will announce it soon.
곧 발표할 예정입니다.
I will know if it is announced.
발표되면 알겠습니다.
"inbox"
"받은 편지함"
"Forward: List of applicants who have passed the selection process"
"앞으로: 선발과정을 통과한 지원자 목록"
What?
무엇?
Yeah? You participated too, right?
응? 당신도 참여했지요?
Tell me, Yoo Jae-min.
말해봐, 유재민.
Hey, wait a minute.
잠깐만요.
"Forward: List of applicants who have passed the selection process"
"앞으로: 선발과정을 통과한 지원자 목록"
knock knock
똑 똑
Chairman Xu Dongxun
쉬동순 회장
a while.
잠시.
The president left work early today.
오늘 대통령은 일찍 퇴근했습니다.
Today I come to see Mr. Park Yoon-jo.
오늘은 박윤조 선생님을 만나러 왔습니다.
I? What's wrong?
나? 뭐가 문제 야?
Do you want to go to dinner together?
같이 저녁 먹으러 갈래?
Why...
왜...
First, I have a suggestion for you.
먼저, 여러분에게 제안할 것이 있습니다.
Have you seen the protein bread sale?
단백질빵 세일 보셨나요?
I do it by myself
나는 그것을 스스로한다
Now he is well-known in the public relations world.
이제 그는 홍보계에서 잘 알려져 있습니다.
Everyone wants to know who I am.
모두가 내가 누구인지 알고 싶어합니다.
This says too much.
이것은 너무 많은 것을 말합니다.
It got a little bit of attention. In the world of digital PR
조금 주목을 받았죠. 디지털 PR의 세계에서
this is not me.
이건 내가 아니야.
Promoting protein bread is me.
단백질빵을 홍보하는 건 나다.
Yes, I can accept that.
네, 받아들일 수 있습니다.
Are you here to tease me?
나를 놀리려고 여기 온 거야?
No.
아니요.
So let's go have a drink?
그럼 한잔하러 갈까요?
From what I understand, your neck is stiff.
제가 알기로는 목이 뻣뻣한 것 같아요.
Can I ask what the offer is?
제안이 무엇인지 물어봐도 될까요?
Is this here?
여기인가요?
Do you want me to stand up and talk?
제가 일어나서 얘기해 드릴까요?
"Forward: List of applicants who have passed the selection process"
"앞으로: 선발과정을 통과한 지원자 목록"
"Some candidates have been selected. Three people in total..."
"일부 후보자가 선정되었습니다. 총 3명입니다..."
OK
좋아요
I'm here to invite you to work.
나는 당신을 직장에 초대하기 위해 왔습니다.
Serve as a leader on one of the EarthComm teams .
EarthComm 팀 중 하나에서 리더 로 봉사하십시오.
" Park Yoon-joo, Strategic Management Department and Public Relations Department"
" 박윤주 전략경영부, 홍보부장 "
"The characters, events, organizations, and backgrounds in the play are all fictitious."
"극중 인물, 사건, 조직, 배경은 모두 허구입니다."
Narrated by Thicha Leelawongpanich
Thicha Leelawongpanich 내레이션